Guide to the Democratic Socialists of America Records TAM.105
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VIII. Chapters, 1971-2008; 26.06 Linear Feet in 56 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, and 1 folder in 1 shared box; 1.33 Megabytes in 30 computer files
  - New York -- Buffalo, 1975-1985
    - DSOC and DSA, 1975-1985 (Box 193, Folder 7)
  - New York -- Ithaca, 1978-2001 (Box 194, Folder 1-2)
  - New York -- Long Island, 1971-1997
    - NAM, 1971-1976 (Box 194, Folder 3, Box 326, Folder 6)
    - DSOC and DSA -- Long Island/Nassau, 1974-1997 (Box 194, Folder 4-5)
  - NAM New York -- Mid-Hudson, 1975-1976 (Box 326, Folder 7)
  - New York -- New York, 1971-2008
    - NAM, 1971-1972 (Box 326, Folder 8)
    - NAM and DSOC, 1971-1973 (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - NAM, 1973-1974 (Box 326, Folder 9)
    - NAM and DSOC, 1974 (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - NAM and DSOC, 1975 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - NAM, 1975-1981 (Box 327, Folder 1)
    - NAM and DSOC, 1976 (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - NAM and DSOC, 1977 (Box 195, Folder 5)
    - NAM and DSOC, 1978 (Box 195, Folder 6)
    - NAM and DSOC, 1979 (Box 196, Folder 1, Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 17)
    - NAM and DSOC, 1980 (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - NAM and DSOC, 1981 (Box 196, Folder 3-4)
    - NAM and DSOC, 1982 (Box 196, Folder 5, Box 197, Folder 1)
    - DSA, 1983 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - DSA, 1984 (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - DSA, 1985 (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - DSA, 1986 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - DSA, 1987 (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - DSA, 1988 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - DSA, 1989 (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - DSA, 1990 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - DSA, 1991 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - DSA, 1992 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - DSA, 1993 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - DSA, 1994 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - DSA, 1995-1996
      - Correspondence, Newsletters, Meeting Minutes, and Reports (Box 199, Folder 6)
      - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_145
    - DSA, 1997
      - Correspondence, Newsletters, Meeting Minutes, and Reports (Box 200, Folder 1)
      - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_146
    - DSA, 1998-1999
      - Correspondence, Newsletters, Meeting Minutes, and Reports (Box 200, Folder 2)
      - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_147
    - DSA, 2003-2004; TW_TAM_105_ER_148
    - DSA, 2008 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - DSA, 2015 (Box 342, Folder 15)
  - New York -- Rochester, 1980-1993 (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - New York -- Suffolk, 1975-1989
    - NAM, 1975-1976 (Box 327, Folder 2)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1977-1989 (Box 200, Folder 5)
  - New York -- Westchester, 1980-1989 (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - North Carolina, 1973-1977 (Box 200, Folder 7)
  - North Carolina, 1978-1984 (Box 200, Folder 8)
  - NAM North Carolina -- Charlotte Perkins Gilman Chapter, 1973-1976 (Box 327, Folder 3)
  - NAM North Carolina -- Durham, 1972-1976 (Box 327, Folder 4)
  - North Dakota, 1988-1989 (Box 200, Folder 9)
  - Ohio, 1972-1995
    - NAM, 1972-1976 (Box 327, Folder 5)
    - DSOC, 1973-1977 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1978-1983 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - DSA, 1984-1995 (Box 201, Folder 3)
  - Ohio -- Black Swamp, 1983-1989 (Box 201, Folder 4)
  - Ohio -- Central -- Columbus, 1982-1997 (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - Ohio -- Cleveland, 1972-1998
    - NAM, 1972-1981 (Box 327, Folder 6)
    - DSOC, 1979-1981 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1982-1998 (Box 201, Folder 7)
  - Ohio -- Dayton, 1975-1978 (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - Ohio -- Dayton, 1979-1984 (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - NAM Ohio -- Mad River, 1972-1977 (Box 327, Folder 7)
  - NAM Ohio -- Oxford, 1975-1977 (Box 327, Folder 8)
  - NAM Ohio -- Yellow Springs, 1972-1978 (Box 327, Folder 9)
  - Oklahoma, 1973-1976
    - DSOC, 1973-1976 (Box 200, Folder 10)
    - NAM, 1975-1976 (Box 328, Folder 1)
  - Oregon, 1976-1977 (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - Oregon, 1978-1980 (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - Oregon, 1981-1982 (Box 202, Folder 5)
  - Oregon, 1983-1985 (Box 202, Folder 6)
  - Oregon, 1986-2001 (Box 202, Folder 7)
  - Oregon -- Portland, 2018 (Box 342, Folder 16)
  - NAM Oregon -- Portland, 1973-1982 (Box 328, Folder 2)
  - NAM Oregon -- Southern Oregon, 1977-1978 (Box 328, Folder 3)
  - NAM Oregon -- Willamette Valley, 1975-1981 (Box 328, Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania, 1972-1995
    - NAM, 1972-1977 (Box 328, Folder 5)
    - DSOC, 1973-1974 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - DSOC, 1975-1979 (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1980-1995 (Box 203, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania -- Philadelphia, 1972-2007
    - NAM, 1972-1976 (Box 328, Folder 6)
    - NAM, 1977-1981 (Box 328, Folder 7)
    - DSOC, 1978-1980 (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - DSOC, 1981-1982 (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - DSA, 1983-1985 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - DSA, 1986-1989 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - DSA, 1990-2007 (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh, 1971-1997
    - NAM, 1971-1974 (Box 328, Folder 8)
    - DSOC, 1973-1982 (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - NAM, 1975 (Box 329, Folder 1)
    - NAM, 1976 (Box 329, Folder 2)
    - NAM, 1977 (Box 329, Folder 3)
    - NAM, 1978-1981 (Box 329, Folder 4)
    - DSA, 1983-1985 (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - DSA, 1986-1988 (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - DSA, 1989-1997 (Box 205, Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania -- Reading-Berks, 1974-1995 (Box 205, Folder 5)
  - Rhode Island, 1974-1985 (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - NAM Rhode Island -- Providence, 1974-1977 (Box 329, Folder 5)
  - South Carolina, 1977-1979 (Box 206, Folder 2)
  - NAM South Carolina -- Columbia, 1975 (Box 329, Folder 6)
  - South Dakota, 1983-1984 (Box 206, Folder 3)
  - Tennessee, 1975-1984 (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - Tennessee, 1985 (Box 206, Folder 5)
  - Tennessee, 1986 (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - Tennessee, 1987-1989 (Box 206, Folder 7)
  - Texas, 1972-1989
    - NAM and DSOC, 1972-1978 (Box 207, Folder 1, Box 329, Folder 7)
    - DSOC, 1977 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - DSOC, 1978-1980 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1981-1984 (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - DSA, 1985-1989 (Box 207, Folder 5)
  - NAM Texas -- Austin, 1972-1975 (Box 329, Folder 8)
  - NAM Texas -- Austin, 1976 (Box 329, Folder 9)
  - NAM Texas -- Austin, 1977 (Box 329, Folder 10)
  - Utah, 1974-1987 (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - Vermont, 1972-1984
    - NAM, 1972 (Box 330, Folder 1)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1976-1984 (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - Virginia, 1974-1980 (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - Virginia, 1981-1984 (Box 208, Folder 4)
  - Washington, 1971-1979 (Box 208, Folder 5)
  - Washington, 1980-1988 (Box 208, Folder 6)
  - Washington, 1989-1997 (Box 208, Folder 7)
  - Washington -- Seattle, undated (Box 342, Folder 17)
  - NAM Washington -- Seattle, 1971-1979 (Box 330, Folder 2)
  - Washington, D. C./Maryland/Northern Virginia, 1972-1998
    - NAM, 1972-1975 (Box 330, Folder 3)
    - DSOC, 1975-1978 (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - DSOC, 1979-1981 (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1982-1984 (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - DSA, 1985-1986 (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - DSA, 1987-1988 (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - DSA, 1989-1991 (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - DSA, 1992-1994 (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - DSA, 1995-1998 (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - DSA, 2016 (Box 342, Folder 19)
  - West Virginia, 1973-1983 (Box 210, Folder 5)
  - Wisconsin, 1973-1979 (Box 210, Folder 6)
  - Wisconsin, 1980-1982 (Box 210, Folder 7)
  - Wisconsin, 1983-1998 (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - NAM Wisconsin -- Madison, 1972-1981 (Box 330, Folder 4)
  - NAM Wisconsin -- Milwaukee, 1979-1980 (Box 330, Folder 5)
  - Wyoming, 1975-1984 (Box 211, Folder 2)
- Series IX. Events and Publicity, 1967-2015; 22.27 Linear Feet in 41 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 4 flat boxes, 1 record carton, 4 folders in 2 shared boxes, and 1 shared tall manuscript box; 38 sound tape reels; 98 audiocassettes; 60 VHS; 6 U-matic; 15.47 Gigabytes in 250 computer files
  This series consists of event and program materials which reflect DSOC's, NAM's, and DSA's shared goal of progressive reform and a vision of democratic socialism. Included are planning materials (correspondence and memos, budgets, and schedules) for various projects and events sponsored by DSA and its predecessor organizations, such as the Speakers' Bureau, Solidarity Day, Justice for All/Poverty Project, anti-draft and anti-Vietnam war activities rallies, University in Society Project, National Campaign for Peace in the Middle East, and political education. Additionally, there is information on work with other organizations and participation in other organizations' events, such as the Full Employment Action Council and the Democratic National Convention. Corresponding publicity (flyers, posters, articles, and clippings) is included with all events and programs. Also included are audiovisual recordings of television appearances by DSA leaders, sessions from other organizations' conferences, and lectures and talks.
  - League for Industrial Democracy -- Robert Lekachman, February 24, 1967
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0026)
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0027)
  - Labor Institute Sessions, April 6-7, 1968
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0028)
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0029)
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0030)
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0031)
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0032)
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0033)
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0034)
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0035)
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0036)
  - Frances Fox Piven and Roy Innis -- "The Urban Crisis: Views from the Left" -- The New School, February 1970
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0003)
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0004)
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0005)
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0006)
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0007)
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0008)
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0009)
  - League for Industrial Democracy Trade Union Luncheon -- The New School -- Leon Keyserling and Paul Jennys, February-March 1970
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0010)
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0011)
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0012)
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0013)
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0014)
  - Yehoshafat Harkabi Speaking at Unknown Event, October 26, 1970
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0015)
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0016)
    - Audio Recording (Box 76, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0017)
  - Unidentified Conference, circa 1970
    - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0064)
    - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0065)
    - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0066)
    - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0067)
    - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0068)
    - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0069)
    - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0070)
    - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0071)
    - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0072)
    - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0073)
    - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0074)
    - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0075)
    - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0076)
    - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0077)
    - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0078)
    - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0079)
    - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0080)
    - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0081)
    - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0082)
    - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0083)
    - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0084)
    - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0085)
    - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0086)
    - Audio Recording (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0087)
    - Audio Recording (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0088)
    - Audio Recording (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0089)
    - Audio Recording (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0090)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Events and Programs -- General, 1971 (Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 19)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- G.I. Organizing, 1971-1972 (Box 330, Folder 6)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Anti-War Campaign, 1972 (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Honeywell Project, 1972 (Box 330, Folder 7)
  - Democratic National Convention and Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 212, Folder 2)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Food Cooperatives, 1972-1973 (Box 330, Folder 9)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Political Education Program, 1972-1973 (Box 331, Folder 2)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Praxis School, 1972-1973 (Box 331, Folder 3)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1972-1973
    - NAM, 1972 (Box 330, Folder 8, Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 19)
    - DSOC, 1972-1973 (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - NAM, 1973 (Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 19, Box 331, Folder 5)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- North Country/Indochina Peace Campaign, 1972-1974 (Box 330, Folder 10, Box 331, Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 19)
  - Eugene V. Debs-Norman Thomas Dinner, circa 1972-1976 (Box 212, Folder 4)
  - New Democratic Coalition, 1972-1979 (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Campaign '73, 1973 (Box 331, Folder 4)
  - Energy Crisis Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- "Impeach Nixon" with North Country Peace Campaign, 1973-1974 (Box 331, Folder 6, Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 19)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Middle East Statement, 1973-1974 (Box 331, Folder 7)
  - Work with War Resisters League, 1973-1977 (Box 212, Folder 7)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Equal Rights Amendment Support, 1973-1978 (Box 331, Folder 8)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Community Organizing Schools, 1973-1979 (Box 331, Folder 9)
  - Energy Teach-In, April 1974 (Box 212, Folder 8)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1974
    - DSOC (Box 212, Folder 9)
    - NAM (Box 331, Folder 10)
  - Democratic National Convention and Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 212, Folder 10)
  - United Mine Workers Support, 1974-1975 (Box 212, Folder 11)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Speakers Bureau, 1974-1977 (Box 331, Folder 11)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- East Bay/Bay Area Socialist School, 1974-1979 (Box 331, Folder 12, Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 19)
  - Nobel Laureates Call for Economic Alternatives, January-February 1975 (Box 212, Folder 12)
  - Civil Rights March -- Boston, May 1975 (Box 212, Folder 13)
  - Support for Portuguese Democracy, August 1975 (Box 213, Folder 1)
  - Institute for Policy Studies -- National Agenda Meeting, November 1975 (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - "Can We Afford It?" -- Jack Clark Lecture, 1975 (Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 17)
  - Committee for Economic Alternatives Conference -- "Challenging the Economic Crisis: Jobs for All", 1975 (Box 213, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) and New American Movement (NAM) -- Seminars, 1975 (Box 213, Folder 4)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1975
    - DSOC (Box 213, Folder 5)
    - NAM (Box 331, Folder 13)
  - Democracy '76, 1975-1976 (Box 213, Folder 6-8, Box 214, Folder 1-3)
  - Michael Harrington Debates David Rockefeller, Vice President of Chase Manhattan Bank, 1975-1976
    - Correspondence and Flyers (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - Audio Recording, cuid271 (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0249)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Unemployment Counseling and Workers' Rights Centers, 1975-1976 (Box 332, Folder 1)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- People's Power Project, 1975-1978 (Box 214, Folder 5, Box 215, Folder 1-3)
  - Humphrey-Hawkins Full Employment Bill Support, 1975-1978 (Box 215, Folder 4, Box 216, Folder 1-2)
  - Support for J. P. Stevens' Workers, 1975-1978 (Box 216, Folder 3)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Labor Organizing, 1975-1979 (Box 332, Folder 2)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Socialist Community School -- Los Angeles, 1975-1979 (Box 332, Folder 3)
  - Democratic National Convention and Committee, 1976 (Box 216, Folder 4)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Summer Schools, 1976 (Box 332, Folder 4)
  - Support to Counter Advertising Council's Ecomomics Campaign, 1976 (Box 216, Folder 5)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1976
    - DSOC (Box 217, Folder 1)
    - NAM (Box 332, Folder 5, Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 19)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- Recruitment Campaign, January-February 1977 (Box 217, Folder 2)
  - Alternative State and Local Public Policies -- Third Annual Conference, July 1977 (Box 217, Folder 3)
  - Democratic National Convention and Committee, 1977 (Box 217, Folder 4-5)
  - Eugene V. Debs-Norman Thomas Dinner, 1977 (Box 217, Folder 6)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Winter Institute, 1977 (Box 332, Folder 6)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Summer Schools, 1977 (Box 332, Folder 7)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1977 (Box 217, Folder 7)
  - Human Rights Initiatives, 1977-1978 (Box 217, Folder 8)
  - Democratic Agenda, 1977-1982
    - Correspondence, Reports, Meeting Minutes, and Press, 1977-1982 (Box 218, Folder 1-4, Box 219, Folder 1-2, Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 17)
    - Rally, August 15, 1980; cuid268 (Box 164, Audiocassette 105_0218)
  - Work with the Full Employment Action Council, 1977-1982 (Box 219, Folder 3)
  - Meeting on South Korean Unions, February-March 1978 (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - Public Forum with Anselmo Sule, April 1978 (Box 219, Folder 5)
  - Fifth and Fiftieth Celebration for Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee and Michael Harrington, December 1978 (Box 219, Folder 6)
  - Democratic National Convention and Committee, 1978 (Box 219, Folder 7, Box 220, Folder 1)
  - Eugene V. Debs-Norman Thomas Dinner, 1978 (Box 220, Folder 2)
  - Labor Law Reform Bill Support, 1978 (Box 220, Folder 3)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Weekend Training Schools, 1978 (Box 332, Folder 8)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1978 (Box 220, Folder 4)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- "Save Our Jobs and Communities" (SOJAC) Project, 1978-1979 (Box 220, Folder 5)
  - Progressive Alliance, 1978-1980 (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - Michael Harrington Lecture, circa 1978-1981 (Box Shared Tamiment 171, Folder 11)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Events and Programs -- General, circa 1978-1981 (Box 332, Folder 9)
  - Michael Harrington Debates Representative Jack Kemp -- New York, New York, April 25, 1979 (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0250)
  - Eugene V. Debs-Norman Thomas Dinner, 1979 (Box 220, Folder 7)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Summer Schools, 1979 (Box 332, Folder 10)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1979 (Box 220, Folder 8)
  - Unidentified Conference, Chicago, IL, circa late 1970s (Box 165, Audiocassette 105_0255)
  - National Mobilization Against the Draft (NMAD), 1979 (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - National Mobilization Against the Draft (NMAD), 1980 (Box 221, Folder 2-4, Box 222, Folder 1-4, Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 17)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Second City Socialist School, 1979-1980 (Box 332, Folder 11)
  - Women and Social Justice Conference, circa 1979-1980 (Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 17)
  - School for Democratic Socialism -- New York, 1979-1983 (Box 223, Folder 1)
  - "1980's: Plight or Property? A National Conference on the Future of the American Labor Movement", January 1980 (Box 223, Folder 2)
  - Democratic National Committee -- Platform Committee, 1980 (Box 223, Folder 3-5, Box 224, Folder 1)
  - Eugene V. Debs-Norman Thomas Dinner, 1980 (Box 224, Folder 2)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- Summer Leadership Institute, 1980 (Box 224, Folder 3-4)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1980 (Box 224, Folder 5)
  - Michael Harrington Recording, June 16, 1980 (Box 344, Audiocassette 105.0292)
  - Big Business Day, 1980-1981 (Box 224, Folder 6, Box 225, Folder 1-2, Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 17)
  - General Electric (GE) Boycott, 1980-1981 (Box 225, Folder 3)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Work with Committee Against Registration and the Draft, 1980-1982 (Box 332, Folder 12)
  - American Public Health Association (APHA) Convention -- Michael Harrington -- "Crisis in the Public Sector: Challenge to the Public Health", 1981
    - Audio Recording (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0256)
    - Audio Recording (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0257)
  - Eugene V. Debs-Norman Thomas Dinner, 1981 (Box 225, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- Ronald Reagan Recruitment Drive, 1981 (Box 225, Folder 5)
  - Solidarity Day, 1981 (Box 225, Folder 6-7)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1981 (Box 226, Folder 1)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Fair Budget Action Campaign, 1981-1982 (Box 333, Folder 1)
  - Work with CARD (Committee Against Registration and the Draft) and Similar Organizations, 1981-1984 (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - Coalition to End U. S. Intervention in Central America and the Caribbean, 1981-1990 (Box 226, Folder 3-4, Box 227, Folder 1-2, Box Shared Tamiment 171, Folder 11)
  - Eugene V. Debs-Norman Thomas Dinner, 1982 (Box 227, Folder 3)
  - June 12 Rally Against Nuclear Weapons, 1982 (Box 227, Folder 4)
  - Labor Day -- San Francisco, 1982 (Box 227, Folder 5)
  - "Turning Things Around" Conference -- Rutgers University -- New Brunswick, New Jersey, 1982 (Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 17)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1982 (Box 227, Folder 6)
  - Independent Moscow Peace Group, 1982-1983 (Box 227, Folder 7)
  - Speakers' Bureau, 1982-1985 (Box 228, Folder 1)
  - Socialist Elected Officials -- Lists, 1982-1990 (Box 228, Folder 2)
  - "Tax Policy and the Economy: A Debate between Michael Harrington and Jack Kemp -- Moderated by Leonard Silk", March 20, 1983 (Box 157, Vhs 105.0138)
  - Eugene V. Debs-Norman Thomas Dinner, 1983 (Box 228, Folder 3)
  - 20th Anniversary Mobilization for Jobs, Peace and Freedom, 1983 (Box 228, Folder 4, Box Shared Tamiment 171, Folder 11)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1983 (Box 228, Folder 5)
  - Nuclear Disarmament Lecture, circa 1983 (Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 18)
  - Songbook Project, 1983-1984 (Box 228, Folder 6)
  - "After the Elections: What Next for the Left?" Forum, 1984 (Box 228, Folder 7)
  - American Solidarity Movement (ASM), 1984 (Box 228, Folder 8-9)
  - Central America Speakers' Bureau, 1984 (Box 229, Folder 1)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1984 (Box 229, Folder 2-3)
  - Eugene V. Debs-Norman Thomas Dinner, 1984 (Box 229, Folder 4)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1984 (Box 229, Folder 5)
  - Justice for All/Poverty Project, 1984-1986 (Box 229, Folder 6)
  - Justice for All/Poverty Project, 1987
    - Correspondence, Clippings, Programs, and Brochures (Box 229, Folder 7, Box 230, Folder 1-3, Box 231, Box 232, Folder 1)
    - Public Service Spots (Box 163, Quarter inch audio reel 105.0037)
    - "America" (Box 161, Vhs 105.0194)
  - Justice for All/Poverty Project, 1988 (Box 232, Folder 2)
  - Eugene V. Debs-Norman Thomas Dinner, 1988 (Box 232, Folder 3)
  - Michael Harrington Lecture -- Department of Political Science -- Loyola University of Chicago, 1985
    - Audio Recording (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0258)
    - Audio Recording (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0259)
  - New Progressive/Populist Political Movement Meetings, 1985 (Box 232, Folder 4)
  - SANE (National Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy) -- New York Council Conference -- "Independent Initiatives and the Arms Race", 1985 (Box 232, Folder 5)
  - Anti-Apartheid Speaking Tour with Gay Seidman, 1985 (Box 232, Folder 6)